Anna Rusyaeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

SUMMARY

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

SKILLS

- **Agile** (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- Managing projects (Trello, Jira)
- E-commerce (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- **Marketing** (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, moqups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer - Bank 'Tochka'

- User demand analysis
- Marking-up with material design
- · Creating tasks in Trello and Jira
- Making user scenario using moqups
- Creating new components on Angular 2
- Improving usability
- Participate and organization of meetings
- Support written parts

Senior Marketing Manager - 000 'Ideco'

October 2017 – June 2018

July 2018 – present time

- Launch, maintaining and updating websites
- Writing technical specifications for designers and programmers
- Monitoring tasks using Jira and Trello
- Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- SMM
- Activities for attraction leads (mailings, contests, articles in popular magazines, publications in top security channels)
- Typesetting e-mail pages
- Working with mailing lists databases (collect and parsing)
- Creating POS materials



PROJECTS

Test your security



Marketing landing page for creating customer interest through potential threats

Control the traffic



Product landing page, attracting over 1000 people per month.

Happy New Year



Summary page for creating interest in new model

Catalog of projects



Catalog of multi-panel house structures

- Sales analytics
- Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities

SEO Specialist - Advertising Agency 'Index Art'

January 2017 – October 2017

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Designing and correcting a site structure
- Writing technical specifications for revising and updating
- Over 150 closing tasks monitoring
- Creating semantics cores
- Designing and implementation metadata
- Content updating, rendering a page layout
- Creating monthly reports for customers

Context Advertising and SEO Specialist - December 2015 - September 2016

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex.Direct, Google AdWords, MyTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

October 2013 - September 2014

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

Software Engineer -

EDUCATION

- Writing technical specification for software
- Studying functionality of software and detecting its flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing

CERTIFICATIONS

Courses and Certificates: Build Front-End Web Apps from Scratch course

Professional HTML & CSS, level 1

LANGUAGES

Russian – native speaker English – B2

2013

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics February 2015

Master of Computer Science

Ural Federal University 2015

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration

Ural Federal University 2013

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

Ural Federal University

Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic Means To CASI DE CASA DE CAS

Catalog structure

Redesign catalog structure for encreasing the organic traffic by 40%

Domain relocation



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses